Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  - [Clinton inaugural invitations]., Circa 1997]; Series 2; 9 items; 28 x 22 cm. or smaller. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Subjects: Clinton, Bill, 1946- Portraits.; Clinton, Bill, 1946- Inauguration, 1997.; Gore, Al, 1948- Portraits.; Clinton, Bill, 1946- fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00088204; Gore, Al, 1948- fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00184143; 1997 fast; Invitation cards. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh86006388; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Invitation cards. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00978495; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Portraits. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423831; Programs. rbgenr
  - The 53rd Presidential inaugural official guide book by general co-chairs Ann Dibble Jordan, Terence R. McAulliffe; co-executive directors Debbie Willhite, Craig T. Smith., Circa [1997]; Series 2; 80 pages: color illustrations, maps, portraits; 17 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 93
  - Unveiling exercises of tablet on the Friendship House, 324-326 Virginia Avenue S.E., originally the residence of Dr. Frederick May ... Wednesday, October 23, 1929, 4.45 P.M. by under the auspices of the Permanent Committee on Marking Points of Historic Interest in the District of Columbia., Circa [1929]; Series 2; 4 pages; 18 cm (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 94
    Subjects: May, Frederic, 1773-1847 Homes and haunts.; Friendship House Association (Washington, D.C.)
  - The Washington cathedral ..., 1916; Series 2; 16 pages plates, plan 24 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 95
    Subjects: Washington Cathedral. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79058423; Washington Cathedral. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00533104
  - Charter, by-laws and regulations of the Oak-Hill Cemetery Company, Georgetown, D.C., Circa [1849]; Series 2; 10 pages; 22 cm (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 96
    Subjects: Oak-Hill Cemetery (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n95803733; Oak-Hill Cemetery (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00713899; Cemeteries Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85021811; Cemeteries. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00850521; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - National Capitol Trolley Museum souvenir guidebook edited by Randolph Kean [for the] National Capital Historical Museum of Transportation; photographs supplied by Albert L. Cramer ... and others., Circa [1978]; Series 2; 24 unnumbered pages: chiefly illustrations, map; 23 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 97
    Subjects: Railroad museums Maryland Silver Spring Guidebooks.; Railroad museums. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01088634; Maryland Silver Spring. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01207317; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Washington Cathedral: the office for the laying of the foundation stone: feast of St. Michael and all angels, A.D. 1907., Circa [1907]; Series 2; 28 pages; 23 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 98
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Henry Y. Satterlee, Bishop of Washington.
  - World's championship games 1924: Clark Griffith Stadium., Circa [1924]; Series 2; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 99
    Cataloger notes: Ticket for game 7 of the 1924 World series.
    Subjects: World Series (Baseball) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no2001014780; World Series (Baseball) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01409714
  - The American Union and its annex, Washington, D.C.: a study in plan and detail Albert Kelsey and David P. Cret, associate architects; text by C. Matlack Price., 1913; Series 2; pages [385]-457, [3] folded leaves of plates: illustrations, plans; 26 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 100
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Architectural record. Vol. 34, numbers 182 (Nov. 1913).
    Subjects: Pan American Union. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79118117; Pan American Union. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00537741
  - City of Washington and suburbs., Circa [1910]; Series 2; 1 map; 40 x 50 cm, folded in cover 17 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 101
    Cataloger notes: "Copyright, 1910, by Bert S. Elliott."; Accompanied by text: Washington handy book directory and map: streets ... postal information, et cetera 48 pages; 17 cm.; Oriented with north toward the upper left.; Shows radial distances and block numbers.; Available also through the Library of Congress Web site as a raster image.
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) Maps. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117384; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871; Maps. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423704; United States District of Columbia Washington. naf
  - Downtown Washington: a walking guide [prepared by Downtown Progress, with thanks to Ellen Kotz for all graphics and to the D.C. Department of Housing and Community Development for editorial assistance and funding]., Circa [1976?]; Series 2; [16] pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 102
    Cataloger notes: Funded partly by U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development.
    Subjects: Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Places of interest in Washington and vicinity, and how to reach them by compliments of Dulin and Martin Company., Circa [191-?]; Series 2; 48 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 16 cm (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 103
    Cataloger notes: "A handy book for visitors, including time tables of railroads and steamboats."; Cover title.
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Pictorial Washington by compliments of the Washington Board of Trade., Circa [1931?]; Series 2; 32 pages: chiefly illustrations; 26 cm (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 104
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117383; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington Metropolitan Area Description and travel.; Washington (D.C.) Metropolitan Area. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243122; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - A hand-book of Washington by Pennsylvania Railroad, Passenger Dept., Circa [1894]; Series 2; 43 pages: illustrations, 1 folded map; 20 cm (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 105
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Pennsylvania Railroad to Washington.
  - About Washington., Circa [1909]; Series 2; 64 pages, [5] leaves of plates (1 folded): illustrations, map; 16 cm (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 106
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Includes 4 pages of advertisements for Galt and Brother jeweller, Washington, D.C.; Includes index.
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - What to see in Washington (District of Columbia): map and guide book by compliments of American Oil Company., Circa [1940]; Series 2; 17 pages: illustrations, map; 23 x 21 cm folded to 23 x 11 cm (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 107
  - Report of the Washington Canal Company, of their receipts and expenditures, during the year 1822., 1823; Series 2; 3 pages; 24 cm (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 108
    Cataloger notes: "48."; "February 3, 1823. Ordered to lie on the table."; Cover title.; Disbound.
    Subjects: Washington Canal Company. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/nr2001042512; Washington Canal Company. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00769649; Washington Canal (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh88001348; Washington (D.C.) Washington Canal. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01317256
  - The Japanese cherry trees: National Capital parks, Washington, D.C., Circa [192-?]; Series 2; 8 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 109
    Subjects: Cherry Washington (D.C.); Cherry. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00853742; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505
  - The Washington National Monument by Oscar Foote., Circa [1887]; Series 2; pages 691-698: illustrations, portraits; 26 cm (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 110
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: The American magazine. Oct. 1887.; Bryan, W.B. Bib. of the District of Columbia, pages 135
  - A funeral service for the Honorable Thurgood Marshall, 1908-1993: Thursday, January twenty-eighth, one thousand nine hundred and ninety three at eleven o'clock in the morning, Washington National Cathedral, Mount Saint Alban, Washington, D.C., Circa [1993]; Series 2; 12 pages; 22 cm (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 113
    Subjects: Marshall, Thurgood, 1908-1993 Death and burial.; Washington Cathedral. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79058423; Funeral rites and ceremonies Washington (D.C.)
  - Ceremonies attending the presentation of the Wright brothers' aeroplane of 1903 by the estate of Orville Wright: the forty-fifth anniversary of the first flight by Wilbur and Orville Wright at Kitty Hawk, North Carolina, December 17, 1948, ten a.m., North Hall, Arts and Industries Building, United States National Museum, Washington, D.C., Circa [1948]; Series 2; [8] pages: illustrations, portraits, photograph; 26 cm (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 114
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Includes a mounted photograph on pages [6] of the Wright Flyer hanging from the ceiling of the Arts and Industries Building.
    Subjects: Aeronautics United States Flights.; Wright Flyer (Airplane) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh86000359; Aeronautics Flights. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00798335; Wright Flyer (Airplane) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01181606; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Capitol Hill house and garden tour 1997: celebrating our 40th anniversary., Circa [1997]; Series 2; 35 pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 115
  - The Woodley Park Community Association spring house tour: Sunday, April 27, 1997, 1 to 4 pm., Circa [1997]; Series 2; 27 unnumbered pages: illustrations, map; 28 x 11 cm (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 116
    Subjects: Historic buildings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85061106; Historic buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00957723; Woodley Park (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n97021432; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Washington (D.C.) Woodley Park. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01322936
  - Dedication of the Museum of History and Technology of the Smithsonian Institution, January 22, 1964., Series 2; 26 pages illustrations 24 cm. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 117
  - Magna carta: the Lincoln cathedral copy exhibited in the Library of Congress some notes prepared by David C. Mearns and Verner W. Clapp., Circa 1939; Series 2; [4] leaves, 10 pages: illustrations, facsimile (folded); 26 cm (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 118
    Cataloger notes: In illustrated paper covers.
    Subjects: Magna Carta. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50064742; Magna Carta. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01356211
  - Magna carta presentation ceremony., Circa [1976]; Series 2; [8] pages; 21 x 22 cm (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 119
    Cataloger notes: "Master of ceremonies, the Honorable Hugh Scott, Republican Leader, United States Senate."; The Great Rotunda, The Capitol June 3, Nineteen Hundred Seventy-six, Ten thirty o'clock, antemeridian.
    Subjects: American Revolution Bicentennial (1976) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01709740; Magna Carta. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50064742; Magna Carta. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01356211; 1976 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/28307; American Revolution Bicentennial, 1976. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85004412
  - [Washington Monument articles]., Circa [1885?]; Series 2; 11 pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 121
    Cataloger notes: First article reprinted from: Engineering news, March 14 and 28, 1885. Second article reprinted from: Scientific American, March 14, 1885.; In green paper covers.; Title supplied by cataloger.; Will the Washington Monument stand? -- The Washington Monument alleged to be in danger.; Bryan, W.B. Bib. of the District of Columbia, pages 135
  - 30th Dupont Circle house tour: Sunday, October 19, 1997, 12:00 noon to 5:00 PM., Circa [1997]; Series 2; 72 pages: illustrations, map; 22 cm (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 122
  - [National Capital Centennial invitations]., Circa [1900]; Series 2; 6 items; 11 x 14 cm or smaller (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 123
    Cataloger notes: Invitations in an envelope to events for the National Capital Centennial in Washington, D.C., issued by the National Capital Centennial Committee.; Title supplied by cataloger.
    Subjects: Invitation cards. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh86006388; Capitals (Cities) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00846490; Invitation cards. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00978495; United States Capital and capitol. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85139919; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Logan Circle house tour: a Victorian Christmas: Sunday, December 7th, 1997, 1:00-5:00 PM sponsored by Logan Circle Community Association., Circa 1997]; Series 2; 36 pages: illustrations; 27 x 11 cm. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 124
  - Services in St. Paul's Church, Alexandria, Va. January 23, 1910, being its one hundredth anniversary., Circa [1910]; Series 2; 34 pages (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 125
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Centennial Services, St. Paul's Church, Alexandria, Virginia.
    Subjects: St. Paul's Episcopal Church (Alexandria, Va.) History.; St. Paul's Episcopal Church (Alexandria, Va.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00599424; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - National aircraft collection, Smithsonian institution, United States National museum., Circa [1941]; Series 2; 2 preliminary leaves, 43, [1] pages illustrations (including portraits) 24 cm (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 126
    Cataloger notes: Caption title: ... by Paul Edward Garber, assistant curator of engineering in charge Section of aeronautics, U.S. National museum.; Previously published under title: Handbook of the national aircraft collection exhibited in the United State National museum.; Publication 3635.
    Subjects: Aeronautics Exhibitions. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh89001335; Aeronautics History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85001337; Aeronautics. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00798293; Exhibition catalogs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01424028; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Admit one person to the National Museum on the 4th of March, 1881., Circa [1881]; Series 2; 1 sheet; 7 x 12 cm (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 127
    Cataloger notes: Ticket numbers 7946 to the inaugural Ball for President Garfield, 1881.
    Subjects: Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 Inauguration.; Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00004703; Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Washington City and how to see it: a complete pocket guide to all places of interest in the national capital and vicinity., 1876; Series 2; vi, 68, [4] pages, [1] folded leaf of plates: illustrations, map; 16 cm. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 128
    Cataloger notes: Disbound.; Last [4] pages are advertisement.; Text by Robert C. Ogden.; Bryan, W.B. Bib. of the District of Columbia, pages 144
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington Metropolitan Area Guidebooks.; Washington Metropolitan Area Description and travel.; Washington (D.C.) Metropolitan Area. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243122; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - The trinity of the United States of America: the Declaration of Independence, the federal Constitution and the Star spangled banner by [George Washington Drew]., Undated; Series 2; 40 p., [1] leaf of plates: port.; 23 cm. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 129
    Cataloger notes: Copyright by George W. Drew.; In brown paper covers printed in black.
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919.
  - The Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden., Circa [1974]; Series 2; 44 leaves in various foliations; 28 cm (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 130
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Miscellaneous documents pertaining to the opening of the Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden.
    Subjects: Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden. http://id.loc.gov/vocabulary/organizations/dsihms; Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00528252
  - Seventy-fifth anniversary: Central Presbyterian Church, organized May 31, 1868., Circa [1943]; Series 2; 15 pages: illustrations, portrait; 26 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 131
    Subjects: Central Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.) History.; Presbyterians Washington (D.C.); Church buildings Washington (D.C.)
  - The Phillips Collection and related thoughts on art by Duncan Phillips., Circa [196-?]; Series 2; 25 unnumbered pages; 23 x 10 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 132
    Cataloger notes: "A radio talk."; Cover title.
    Subjects: Phillips Collection. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79046255; Phillips Collection. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00532103; Art. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85007461; Art. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00815177
  - Programme of ceremonies of the dedication of Memorial Continenetal Hall by the National Society of the Daughters of the American Revolution: April seventeenth, nineteen hundred and five, ten o'clock, A.M., Circa [1905]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages; 20 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 133
    Subjects: Daughters of the American Revolution. http://id.loc.gov/vocabulary/organizations/dndar; Memorial Continental Hall (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh86006696; Daughters of the American Revolution. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00529444; Memorial Continental Hall (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631664
  - The church of the open door., Circa [192-?]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet: illustrations; 23 x 40 cm folded to 23 x 21 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 134
    Subjects: First Congregational Church (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n96075158; First Congregational Church (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00719317; Church buildings Washington (D.C.); Congregationalists Washington (D.C.); Church buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00860599; Congregationalists. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00875214; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Programme of organization of the Smithsonian Institution presented to the Board of Regents, Dec. 8, 1847 [by Joseph Henry]., Circa [1847?]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages; 27 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 135
    Subjects: Smithsonian Institution. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79053968; Smithsonian Institution. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00532691
  - Wesley Hall: Lorton S. Wesley, owner: District 1700, 1703 K Street, N.W., Washington, D.C., Circa [193-?]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (8 pages): illustrations; folded to 23 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 136
    Subjects: Wesley Hall (Washington, D.C.); Hotels Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85062504
  - For President, Ulysses S. Grant: for Vice-President, Henry Wilson ... election, Tuseday, November 5, 1872., Circa [1872]; Series 2; 1 sheet; frame 20 x 12 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 137
    Subjects: Grant, Ulysses S. (Ulysses Simpson), 1822-1885. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n2007080261; Wilson, Henry, 1812-1875. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/nb2010001470; Grant, Ulysses S. (Ulysses Simpson), 1822-1885 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00061535; Wilson, Henry, 1812-1875 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00266656; Presidents United States Election. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106475; Presidents Election. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075747; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Reflections on the African American experience in Washington, 1968-1998 by William Raspberry [and others]., Circa [1998]; Series 2; 36 pages: illustrations (some color), portraits; 27 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 138
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Special issue of the Washington post magazine, Feb. 1, 1998.; Then and now / by Eugene Robinson --- The structure of change / by Michael A. Fletcher -- Landscape: U street / by Mary Battiata -- Home rule and its discontents / by Colbert I. King -- The meanings of funk / by Kenneth Carroll -- Landscape: Perrywood / by David Finkel -- Toward 2028 / by William Raspberry.
    Subjects: African Americans Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009114063; African Americans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00799558; Manners and customs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01007815; Washington (D.C.) Social life and customs. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145361; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505